<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>TailorMeSwiftly.com Release Notes</title>
    <link>https://tailormeswiftly.com</link>
    <description>Latest updates and new features for TailorMeSwiftly.com — the AI-powered resume tailoring tool.</description>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 12:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://tailormeswiftly.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>

    <item>
      <title>v3.4.0 — Kanban Tracker, Notes &amp; Company Intel</title>
      <link>https://tailormeswiftly.com/updates.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">tailormeswiftly-v3.4.0</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[
        <ul>
          <li><strong>Kanban Application Tracker:</strong> Your applications now live on a full drag-and-drop Kanban board with five columns — Tailored, Applied, Interviewing, Offer, and Rejected.</li>
          <li><strong>Click-to-Open Cards:</strong> Click any Kanban card to open a detail modal with notes, a "Go to Application" button, and Save/Cancel controls.</li>
          <li><strong>Application Notes:</strong> Add free-form notes to any application — interview dates, contact names, follow-up reminders.</li>
          <li><strong>Interview Details:</strong> Cards in the Interviewing column surface structured fields for interview date, contacts, and follow-ups.</li>
          <li><strong>Company Intel:</strong> The Introduction Email page now auto-fetches recent news and insights about your target company.</li>
          <li><strong>Light Theme Default:</strong> The app now defaults to light mode for new users.</li>
          <li><strong>UI Polish:</strong> Opaque dropdown menus, wider navigation labels, and improved auth session handling.</li>
        </ul>
      ]]></description>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>v3.3.0 — Past Applications &amp; History</title>
      <link>https://tailormeswiftly.com/updates.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">tailormeswiftly-v3.3.0</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[
        <ul>
          <li><strong>Past Applications:</strong> All your generated resumes, cover letters, interview Q&A, and outreach emails are now automatically saved to your account.</li>
          <li><strong>One-Click Restore:</strong> Instantly reload any previous application's outputs without re-generating.</li>
          <li><strong>Incremental Saves:</strong> When you generate a cover letter, interview questions, or outreach email on-demand, the save updates automatically.</li>
          <li><strong>History Navigation:</strong> Quick links to Past Applications are now available throughout the app.</li>
        </ul>
      ]]></description>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>v3.2.0 — Voice, Reliability &amp; Design</title>
      <link>https://tailormeswiftly.com/updates.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">tailormeswiftly-v3.2.0</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[
        <ul>
          <li><strong>ElevenLabs TTS:</strong> Mock interview questions are now read aloud using a premium ElevenLabs AI voice, with browser TTS as a fallback.</li>
          <li><strong>Reliable Job URL Fetching:</strong> Pasting a job listing URL now fetches through our own server, replacing old third-party proxies.</li>
          <li><strong>Resume Quick Presets:</strong> Redesigned preset buttons with color-coded accent dots.</li>
          <li><strong>Use Last Resume:</strong> Returning users can instantly load their previously uploaded resume.</li>
          <li><strong>Results Page Refresh:</strong> Updated header and background to match the main app's look and feel.</li>
          <li><strong>Improved Skill Chips:</strong> Missing skills now have higher-contrast colors in both themes.</li>
          <li><strong>Personalized Greeting:</strong> A "Hi, [Name]" greeting now appears under your avatar.</li>
        </ul>
      ]]></description>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>v3.1.0 — UX Polish &amp; Improvements</title>
      <link>https://tailormeswiftly.com/updates.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">tailormeswiftly-v3.1.0</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[
        <ul>
          <li><strong>10 Mock Interview Questions:</strong> Increased from 8 to 10 tailored interview questions.</li>
          <li><strong>Improved Text-to-Speech:</strong> More natural voice delivery with optimized rate and pitch.</li>
          <li><strong>Dark Resume Preset:</strong> New high-contrast "Dark" theme for maximum readability.</li>
          <li><strong>Results Grid Layout:</strong> All 4 outputs now display in a single row.</li>
          <li><strong>Updated Homepage:</strong> Cleaner header design with TailorMeSwiftly.com branding above the animation.</li>
          <li><strong>Removed LinkedIn Optimization:</strong> Streamlined feature set to focus on core strengths.</li>
          <li><strong>Enhanced Loading Experience:</strong> Improved funny quotes display.</li>
          <li><strong>Messaging Refresh:</strong> Updated homepage copy to highlight lightning-fast results.</li>
        </ul>
      ]]></description>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>v3.0.0 — Major Update</title>
      <link>https://tailormeswiftly.com/updates.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">tailormeswiftly-v3.0.0</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[
        <ul>
          <li><strong>Gaps Assistant:</strong> Renamed and refined the skill gap analysis step.</li>
          <li><strong>Mock Interview Mode:</strong> Hear questions read aloud with TTS. Practice one at a time with AI-powered feedback on recorded answers.</li>
          <li><strong>On-Demand Generation:</strong> Interview prep and email drafts generate only when you click their tab, making initial tailoring faster.</li>
          <li><strong>Application Tracker Fix:</strong> Kanban board now loads from the cloud with persistent drag-and-drop.</li>
          <li><strong>Resume Versions:</strong> All tailored resumes saved with version names. View and reload any past version.</li>
          <li><strong>Saved Jobs:</strong> Bookmark job descriptions and tailor resumes against them later.</li>
          <li><strong>Career Profile:</strong> Store a master career history in Preferences.</li>
          <li><strong>Loading Redesign:</strong> Full-screen centered loading overlay with blurred background.</li>
          <li><strong>Preferences Dropdown:</strong> Accessible from a clean dropdown on your profile avatar.</li>
          <li><strong>Generation Timeout:</strong> API calls now have timeouts with retry buttons.</li>
        </ul>
      ]]></description>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>v2.1.0 — Missing Skills Analysis Engine</title>
      <link>https://tailormeswiftly.com/updates.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">tailormeswiftly-v2.1.0</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[
        <ul>
          <li><strong>Design Customization:</strong> Granularly tweak typography, accent colors, and layout spacing.</li>
          <li><strong>Target Company Preset:</strong> Extracts brand colors of your targeted company and injects them into your resume.</li>
          <li><strong>Missing Skills Extraction:</strong> Automated extraction of job requirements missing from your resume.</li>
          <li><strong>AI Co-Pilot Integration:</strong> Select missing skills you possess and our engine weaves them into your bullet points.</li>
          <li><strong>Bug Fix:</strong> Resolved the routing issue where the Application Tracker blanked out.</li>
        </ul>
      ]]></description>
    </item>

  </channel>
</rss>
